Eichmann is a history, drama film directed by Robert Young.
Based upon the final confession of Adolf Eichmann, made before his execution in
Israel, of his role in Hitler's plan for the final solution.
Adolf Eichmann, played by Thomas Kretschmann.
Avner Less, played by Troy Garity.
Vera Less, played by Franka Potente.
Minister Tormer, played by Stephen Fry.
Miriam Fröhlich, played by Delaine Yates.
Baroness Ingrid von Ihama, played by Tereza Srbova.
Eichmann is a biographical film detailing the interrogation of Adolf Eichmann.
Directed by Robert Young, the film stars Thomas Kretschmann as Eichmann and
Troy Garity as Eichmann's Israeli interrogator, Avner Less.
It was first released in Brazil in September 2007, and was
released in the United States in October 2010.
The film explores themes of nazi, world war ii, post
world war ii, crime against humanity.
The tone is emotional.